<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to BAO! on BAO</title>
    <link>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to BAO! on BAO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://UIC-BAO.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>To get in contact with our team, please feel free to either email us at uic.bao.master@gmail.com or to make use of the form below.
​
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/board/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/board/</guid>
      <description>BAO is led by the following Students and Faculty Partners.
​
Board Chris Kerwell Gresla - President &amp;amp; Benevolent Dictator
Born and raised in Chicago, Chris loves bodybuilding, programming, philosophy and life. He currently is a Graduate Research Assistant for the Center of Applied analytics.
Tejaswi Cherukuri - VP, Treasury &amp;amp; Finance
Tejaswi is pursuing her Master’s in Business Analytics. She is a Mechanical Engineer and worked as a Quality Specialist for a major firm in India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership</title>
      <link>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/membership/</guid>
      <description>The Business Analytics Organization (BAO) is a student organization that fosters interaction and networking with industry experts and leaders in the field of analytics and data science. Workshops and networking events expose students to different technologies and application areas.
​
Becoming a BAO Member
To become a BAO member the steps are as follows-
 5 Fee to be assessed by quick-paying (Zelle) our Treasurer, Tejaswi Cherukuri. (see contact information below)  Once we receive your payment, Tejaswi will reach out with an email and link to our membership information survey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Session - Shruti Tanksali</title>
      <link>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/events/ss-shrutitanksali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://UIC-BAO.github.io/events/ss-shrutitanksali/</guid>
      <description>​
Event Details
 Location: Virtual via Zoom (link to be distributed to all RSVP respondents) Time: February 25th from 2pm to 3pm (Central) RSVP Link: https://forms.gle/KWAvQXRfQu7K7ky47  ​
Shruti is a Business Analytics Partner at Facebook (Meta) and has previously worked as an Analyst for Google, Humana and Walmart. This session will start off with a brief background about her career thus far and will then will transition to an open Q&amp;amp;A.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
